One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Aqua Laguna
‫أكوا لاغونا‬
She jumped off into the Backstreets!
‫لقد قفزت نحو الأزقة الخلفيّة‬
– Wait! – Don't go down there!
‫مهلًا، عودي حالًا!‬
Don't go after her!
‫لا تتبعوها‬
Mr. Paulie!
‫باولي-سان!‬
All of you rushing off isn't going to save her!
‫لن يكون ذهابكم جميعًا‬ ‫كافيًا لإنقاذها على أيّ حال!‬
But...!
‫لكن...‬
It's the sea we're up against!
‫إنّنا نواجه البحر هنا،‬ ‫ستتشاركون نفس المصير!‬
If something happens, I'll take care of it.
‫إن حدث أمر ما، سأتولّى الأمور بنفسي‬
To think she'd run straight into danger...
‫أما تخشى الركض هناك؟‬
That girl is something else!
‫إنّها امرأة مميّزة!‬
Idiots! Be impressed later!
‫أغبياء! هذا ليس وقتًا مناسبًا لتظهروا إعجابكم!‬
Hey! Get back here right now!
‫اسمعي! عودي في الحال!‬
You'll be swallowed by the sea!
‫سيبتلعك البحر‬
A sea anemone...
‫شقائق نعمان البحر...‬
A sea anemone is coming out of a chimney.
‫شقائق نعمان البحر تخرج من مدخنة،‬ ‫شقائق نعمان البحر؟!‬
A sea anemone?
‫شقائق نعمان البحر؟‬
Hey, wait, reindeer! Not you, too!
‫انتظر أيّها الرّنّة! لا تذهب أيضًا!‬
Zoro!
‫زورو!‬
Pirate lady! You're so amazing!
‫أنتِ رائعة يا أختي القرصانة‬
So impetuous!
‫يا للحماقة‬
There's no way she'll make it back in time!
‫لن تعودي في الوقت المناسب‬
Just look offshore!
‫انظري للسّاحل، الموجة تقترب‬
This is bad! They're done for!
‫مصيبة، سيموتان!‬
There's no saving them now!
‫لا نستطيع إنقاذهما‬
Zoro! Zoro!
‫زورو، زورو! أيمكنك سماعي؟! هذا أنا!‬
Chopper?
‫تشوبر؟‬
It's no use...
‫لا فائدة، لا أستطيع التّقدّم أكثر‬
Luffy!
‫لوفي!‬
What the hell are you doing there?!
‫أيّها الأحمق، ما الذي تفعله هناك؟!‬
N-Nami! Are you behind me?!
‫نا... نامي! هل أنتِ خلفي؟‬
Well, hey, listen!
‫اسمعيني‬
See, that pigeon jerk sent me flying, and I got stuck in this gap.
‫لقد قذفني صاحب الحمامة‬ ‫ثمّ هبطت وعلقت في هذه الفجوة‬
Quit messing around at a time like this!
‫كفاك عبثًا في وقتٍ حرج كهذا‬
While you've been goofing off, Robin was taken away!
‫لقد أخذوا روبين بينما أنت تلهو‬
Robin's giving up her life for us!
‫تنوي روبين الموت من أجلنا‬
She sacrificed herself to protect us from the government!
‫روبين ضحّت بحياتها لحمايتنا من هجوم حكومة العالم‬
I have nowhere to go and no home to return to.
‫ليس لدي مكان أذهب أو أعود إليه‬
No. We're through.
‫بلى، انتهى.‬ ‫لن أراكم ثانيةً أبدًا.‬
Even though she knew that being taken away would mean her death!
‫وافقت على الذهاب معهم وهي تعرف أنّهم سيقتلونها!‬
So...
‫إذًا...‬
Robin was...
‫فقد كانت روبين...‬
lying all along?
‫تكذب علينا؟‬
Yes!
‫نعم!‬
I'm so glad...
‫طمأنتِني!‬
Don't worry!
‫لا تقلقي‬
I'm not gonna let Robin die!
‫لن أدع روبين تموت!‬
Look at that wave!
‫انظروا لتلك الموجة‬
What the hell is that?! It's so much bigger than usual!
‫ما هذا؟! إنها أكبر بأضعاف من المعتاد‬
Hey! This is seriously bad!
‫مهلاً، هذا خطير جدًّا‬
Pirate woman! Give up and run already!
‫أيّتها القرصانة! استسلمي واهربي!‬
Reindeer!
‫أيّها الرّنّة‬
I'm being torn apart!
‫هذا مؤلم، تكاد تمزّقني‬
You're really stuck in there!
‫إنّك تأبى أن تخرج‬ ‫كيف علقت هنا يا زورو؟!‬
Quit pulling on me!
‫هذا مؤلم، لا تسحبني!‬
What are we gonna do?! That huge wave is almost here!
‫ما العمل الآن؟‬ ‫الموجة الضخمة تقترب منا!‬
"What are we gonna do", huh?
‫"ما الّذي سنفعله؟"‬ ‫وما أدراني؟‬
Hey, wait a sec.
‫مهلاً لحظة، أتحمل كيتيتسو معك؟‬
Huh? Your sword?
‫أتقصد هذا السيف؟‬ ‫نعم إنه معي‬
How'd you know?
‫كيف عرفت؟‬
Since that one's cursed, I can tell when it's around.
‫لأنه سيفٌ ملعون، بوسعي أن أستشعر لعنته‬
So you kept it for me, Chopper?
‫إذًا فقد كنت تحمله من أجلي يا تشوبر؟‬
Thanks.
‫شكرًا لك‬
Put it in my hand! Quick!
‫دعني أمسكه في يدي، بسرعة!‬
Make a run for it!
‫اهربي بسرعة‬
You have to climb up high! Get to high ground!
‫تسلّقي لمكان عالٍ! اذهبي لأعلى مكان!‬
It's no use! They're done for!
‫لا فائدة! لن ينجحوا في الوقت المناسب!‬
You're gonna be swallowed!
‫سيبتلعك البحر!‬
Aqua Laguna is here!
‫قد ضربت أكوا لاغونا!‬
What is this...?
‫ما هذا...؟‬
This is it!
‫لا فائدة‬
What the hell?! He busted up those buildings!
‫ما هذا؟! لقد حطّم المبنيين!‬
Zoro!
‫زورو!‬
Stay back, Chopper!
‫تراجع يا تشوبر!‬
One-Sword Style:
‫أسلوب السّيف الواحد‬ ‫إيتوريو‬
Thirty-Six-Pound Phoenix!
‫مدفع العنقاء ذي السّتّ والثّلاثين رطل‬ ‫سانجو رووك بوندهو‬
What the hell are they?!
‫ما بال أولئك الأشخاص؟!‬
Here we go, Nami!
‫لنذهب يا نامي‬
What the hell is this?
‫ما هذا؟‬
Rumble! Jumping Point!
‫نقطة تعزيز القفز‬ ‫رامبل جامبينغ بوينت‬
Hold on to me, Zoro!
‫تمسّك بي يا زورو‬
The Backstreets are...!
‫إنّ الأزقة الخلفيّة!...‬
Dammit!
‫سُحقًا‬
Hey!
‫انظروا إلى هناك، ها هم‬
Wow! You made it!
‫أجل! نجحتم!‬
They'll be safe on the bridge.
‫سيكونون بخير بما أنّهم وصلوا للجسر العظيم‬
Even that enormous wave won't reach them there.
‫رغم ضخامة تلك الموجة،‬ ‫إلا أنها لن تصل إليهم‬
You're all amazing!
‫أنتم رائعون‬
Nice job, you guys!
‫أحسنتم يا رفاق‬
It's come this far!
‫لقد وصلت حتّى هنا‬
What happened to the Straw Hats?!
‫ماذا حدث لقراصنة قبّعة القشّ؟!‬
Did Aqua Laguna swallow them?!
‫هل ابتلعتهم أكوا لاغونا؟!‬
No, look at that!
‫كلّا، انظروا‬
Mr. Paulie!
‫باولي-سان!‬
Dammit!
‫سُحقًا‬
We're not in the clear yet! Run!
‫ما زلنا في خطر، اركضوا!‬ ‫اركضوا إلى جزيرة السفانة!‬
Hurry!
‫أسرعوا‬
The bridge is collapsing!
‫سينهار الجسر العظيم!‬
What a wave...
‫يا لها من موجة...‬
Yeah... Unbelievable... This is Shipyard Island!
‫نعم... هذا لا يصدّق...‬ ‫إنّنا في جزيرة السفانة!‬
Even here, I don't feel safe.
‫حتّى البقاء هنا لا يبدو آمنًا‬
Look! The tide is ebbing again.
‫ًانظروا! إنّ الجزْر ينحسر ثانية‬
Of course it is, meaning there'll be more to come!
‫هذا طبيعيّ، ستستمرّ في القدوم‬
A second wave... Then a third...
‫الموجة الثّانية... ثمّ الثّالثة...‬ ‫ستكونان كالتي شهدناها توًّا!‬
We should flee to higher ground as well!
‫لنلتجئ إلى مكان أعلى‬
Seriously... That was reckless!
‫كان ذلك عملاً متهوّرًا‬
Thanks. You saved us, rope guy.
‫شكرًا لك. لقد أنقذتنا يا رجل الحبال.‬
I was shocked!
‫كنت متفاجئة! تلك هي أكوا لاغونا إذًا...‬
I can't stop shaking.
‫ما زلت أرتجف‬
If it was that big every year, the whole island would be long gone.
‫لو كانت تضربنا موجة ضخمة كهذه كل سنة،‬ ‫لاندثرت جزيرتنا منذ وقت طويل‬
It's different this year.
‫ولكن الموجة مختلفة هذه السنة‬
You bunch are crazy!
‫إنكم متهورون حقًا‬
I'm surprised you survived.
‫أنا متفاجئة من نجاتكم‬
Old monster lady!
‫الجدة المتوحشة!‬ ‫أتيتِ إلى هذه الجزيرة إذًا؟‬
Of course!
‫بالطّبع، لو بقينا في عرض‬ ‫البحر لغرقنا!‬
Pirate guy!
‫كنتَ رائعًا يا أخي القرصان!‬
Yeah, I kinda was.
‫نوعًا ما‬
Are you trying to suffocate me?!
‫هل تحاول خنقي؟!‬
This moron passed out while latched onto me.
‫فقد هذا الغبيّ وعيه بينما كان يتشبّث بي‬
Come to think of it, Zoro, why were you also running from the wave?
‫بالمناسبة يا زورو،‬ ‫لماذا كنت تهرب من الموجة؟‬
Were you in the Backstreets?
‫هل كنتَ في المدينة؟‬
Huh? Well... Not exactly...
‫ا... اعفني من الإجابة عن سؤالك.‬
He got stuck in a chimney.
‫كان عالقًا في مدخنة‬
Stuck in a chimney?
‫عالق في مدخنة؟‬
Zoro, you're so careless!
‫يا لك من أخرق يا زورو‬
How do you get yourself in that kind of–
‫كيف حدث هذا؟‬
And who are you to be laughing at others?!
‫أنت آخر من يحق له السخرية!‬
You're both super careless!
‫كلاكما أخرقان‬
So, what happened to Sanji and Uso–
‫أين سانجي وأوسو...‬
I mean, Sanji?
‫أعني سانجي‬
That's right...
‫صحيح... ثمّة أشياء كثيرة لأخبرك بها‬ ‫استمع أيضًا يا زورو‬
This is my big chance.
‫هذه هي فرصتي الكبيرة‬
With a buster call, we can urgently summon
‫باستخدام "نداء الدّمار"، نستطيع استدعاء...‬
five vice admirals from Marine Headquarters along with ten battleships.
‫خمسة من نوّاب أميرالات البحريّة‬ ‫إضافة لعشر سفن حربيّة‬
It's all thanks to Aokiji for giving us, CP9, the authority to execute it.
‫وهذا بفضل أوكيجي الّذي منحنا نحن‬ ‫السّي بي 9 الحقّ لنمارس هذه السّلطة‬
Isn't that right, Funkfreed?
‫ألا تظنّ ذلك يا فانكفريد؟‬
Nico Robin, the woman whom the World Government
‫نيكو روبين، المرأة الّتي لاحقتها‬ ‫الحكومة لعشرين سنة،‬
pursued for twenty years, has fallen straight into CP9's hands.
‫قد وقعت مباشرة بين أيدينا‬ ‫نحن السّي بي 9‬
At the same time, we're also hauling in that rotten Cutty Flam,
‫وفي نفس الوقت، قبضنا على كاتي فلام المقيت ذاك‬
Tom's disciple who possesses the blueprints for Pluton.
‫تلميذ توم الّذي يملك مخطّطات بلوتون‬
In this vast world, they're the only two humans holding the keys to reviving that ancient weapon.
‫ثمّة شخصان فقط يحملان مفتاح‬ ‫السّلاح العتيق في هذا العالم‬
They're on the sea train, heading toward me this very moment...
‫وهذان الاثنان على متن القطار‬ ‫البحريّ ومتّجهان إليّ الآن...‬
That world-shattering armament is headed my way.
‫قوّة عسكريّة قويّة بما يكفي‬ ‫لتدمير العالم في طريقها إليّ‬
There's nothing to think about.
‫لا يوجد ما يدعو للتّفكير بشأنه‬
Let's sail after them right away!
‫لنبحر في الحال ونتبعهم!‬
That's our only choice.
‫لا خيار آخر‬
Hey, rope guy.
‫يا رجل الحبال‬
Please lend us a ship.
‫أعرنا سفينة رجاءً‬
No, instead of a ship, are there other sea trains leaving?
‫أو أهناك قطار بحري سيغادر قريبًا؟‬
The Puffing Tom is the world's one and only sea train.
‫بافينغ توم هو القطار البحري الوحيد في العالم‬
It's a miraculous ship that is the result
‫إنّها سفينة إعجازيّة كانت نتيجة...‬
of the combined efforts of the legendary Tom's Workers.
‫الجهود المجتمعة لفريق بقيادة سفان أسطوريّ‬
Then, let us borrow a ship.
‫حسنًا، أعرنا سفينة ما‬ ‫أقوى وأسرع سفينة في المدينة!‬
Enough already, you idiots!
‫كفى أيّها الأوغاد‬
Weren't you paying attention just now?!
‫ألم تروا ما حدث قبل قليل؟!‬
You were almost pulled out to sea by that wave!
‫كاد البحر أن يسحبكم بتلك الموجة‬
He's right! There's no way you can set out to sea right now!
‫معه حق، لا يمكنكم الإبحار حاليًا!‬
Are you stupid?!
‫هل أنت مجنون؟!‬
No ship has made it through even the usual Aqua Laguna!
‫لم تنجُ أي سفينة من ظاهرة أكوا لاغونا الاعتيادية من قبل!‬
You saw the Backstreets collapse, right?
‫شهدتم بأم أعينكم كيف دُمرت الأزقة الخلفيّة‬
This town, which has always endured Aqua Laguna...
‫هذه المدينة التي عانت دائمًا من أكوا لاغونا...‬
is now in ruins.
‫أمست خرابًا‬
As you can see, the Aqua Laguna this year is unfathomably huge.
‫وفوق ذلك، أكوا لاغونا الّتي‬ ‫ضربتنا هذه السّنة أضخم بكثير‬
If you set out in a ship now, even if you braved it in the largest galleon,
‫إن أبحرتم الآن، فحتّى إن تحدّيتموها‬ ‫بأكبر سفينة شراعية،‬
your ship would be destroyed in an instant.
‫فستحطّم السّفينة في لحظات‬
I can't let you sail out knowing I'm sending you to your deaths.
‫لن أمنحكم سفينة وأنا أعرف بأنكم ذاهبون على متنها إلى حتفكم‬
Wait until morning.
‫انتظروا حتّى الصّباح‬
After the storm, I'll lend you a ship.
‫فسأعيركم سفينة حالما تنتهي العاصفة‬
Hey, you guys. Go to the evacuation site or someplace.
‫وأنتم يا رفاق اذهبوا إلى ملاجئ الإخلاء أو ما شابه‬
We're done searching for people.
‫فقد انتهينا من مهمة البحث عن المفقودين‬
If...
‫إن...‬
If we wait until morning, do we have any chance of success?
‫إن انتظرنا حتى الصباح، فهل سنستطيع تحقيق مُرادنا؟‬
I know all about Enies Lobby.
‫أعرف إنيس لوبي‬
When I heard it was a government island, I remembered...
‫عندما عرفتُ أنّها جزيرة تابعة‬ ‫للحكومة، تذكّرت أمرًا‬
Isn't that...
‫أليس ذلك المكان...‬
Isn't that the place where the Gates of Justice are?
‫أليس ذلك المكان حيث توجد بوّابات العدالة؟‬
What are you talking about?
‫وما هو هذا المكان؟‬
Enies Lobby is the government-owned Judicial Island.
‫إنيس لوبي هي جزيرة قضائيّة تملكها الحكومة‬
But that island is a court in name alone.
‫وبها ما يُسمى محكمة، لكنها اسمٌ فحسب‬
Being taken to Enies Lobby itself is considered to be proof of guilt.
‫جر الشخص إلى إنيس لوبي دليلٌ دامغ على إجرامه‬
After passing through this empty courthouse uninterrupted,
‫بعد المرور بهذه المحكمة الخالية دون توقّف،‬
criminals soon reach huge, cold steel doors.
‫يبلغ المجرمون بوّابات فولاذيّة ضخمة وباردة‬
These doors are called the Gates of Justice.
‫وتلك البوّابات تُعرف ببوّابات العدالة‬
Once criminals go through them,
‫حالما يعبرها المجرم،‬
they'll never see the sunlight again. They're doors of despair.
‫فلن يروا نور الشّمس بعدها أبدًا،‬ ‫إنّها بوّابات يأس‬
After sailing from the harbor beyond those gates,
‫وما إن تبحر من الميناء وراء تلك البوابات،‬
there are only two places you can reach.
‫لا وجهة إلا مكانين اثنين‬
One is considered the mightiest summit of the forces of justice in the world:
‫الوجهة الأولى هي أعتى قوة للعدالة في العالم‬
Marine Headquarters.
‫مقر البحرية‬
The other is the enormous undersea prison, Impel Down,
‫والآخر هو سجن ضخم قابعٌ في أعماق البحر‬
home to vicious prisoners who once ran amok all over the world,
‫حيث غرف التّعذيب والمشانق تتواجد جنبًا‬ ‫إلى جنب، ويحتجز سجناء خبيثين...‬
where torture rooms and gallows stand side by side.
‫عاثوا فسادًا في كلّ العالم‬
To put it simply,
‫بعبارة أخرى،‬
Enies Lobby is just a hollow imitation of justice,
‫إنيس لوبي هي مؤسّسة قضائيّة‬ ‫يُلقى فيها المجرمون،‬
where criminals are condemned with no hope for mercy.
‫دون إظهار أيّ رحمة!‬
Isn't that right?!
‫أليس هذا صحيحًا؟‬
Robin's got a bounty on her head.
‫ثمّة مكافأة على رأس روبين‬
No matter her destination, only hell awaits her!
‫لا يهم أين سيأخذونها، فما ينتظرها هو التعذيب!‬
Every second we waste talking, she gets closer to the Gates of Justice!
‫في كل لحظة تمضي ونحن هنا، تقترب روبين أكثر من بوابات العدالة!‬
There's no way we can wait until morning!
‫يستحيل أن ننتظر حتى الصباح!‬
If you know that much, I've got only one thing to say.
‫ما دمتِ تعرفين كل هذا، فسأضيف شيئًا واحدًا‬
Even if the sea were calm and you were able to sail out,
‫حتى لو هدأت الأمواج الآن وتمكنتم من الإبحار...‬
you should never go there.
‫فلا يجدر بكم الذهاب إلى ذلك المكان‬
Don't forget that you guys are also pirates.
‫لا تنسوا أنكم قراصنة‬
Like you said, Enies Lobby is the front door to the hub of the World Government.
‫كما قلتِ، إنيس لوبي هي المدخل الذي يؤدي إلى مركز حكومة العالم‬
Naturally, taking that into account, it's heavily fortified.
‫وبطبيعة الحال، بجب الأخذ في الحسبانِ‬ ‫وجودَ جبهة قتاليّة للدّفاع عن ذلك‬
No pirate would dream of rescuing a crew member taken to that island...
‫ما من قرصان قد يفكّر في استعادة‬ ‫عضو من طاقمه أُخِذ لتلك الجزيرة...‬
because the outcome is certain.
‫لأنّ ما سيحدث واضح وضوح الشّمس‬
Are you trying to pick a fight in the very heart of the World Government?!
‫هل تحاولون افتعال قتال‬ ‫في مركز حكومة العالم؟!‬
H-He's right! You should give up!
‫إ-إنّه على حقّ! انسوا الأمر‬
Aqua Laguna won't let you sail until morning!
‫لن تستطيعوا الإبحار حتى الصباح بسبب أكوا لاغونا‬
You'll die just going after them!
‫حتّى إن ذهبتم خلفهم، فستُقتلون‬
There's no chance of you guys surviving!
‫فرصة نجاتكم معدومة!‬
Luffy...
‫لوفي...‬
Then, we'll...
‫حسنًا إذًا...‬
steal a ship and go!
‫سنسرق سفينة ونذهب‬
We're gonna sail out now!
‫سنبحر الآن!‬
Our friend is waiting!
‫صديقتنا تنتظرنا!‬
Don't stand in our way!
‫فلا تقفلوا في طريقنا‬
Th-The wave got angry too!
‫حـ-حتّى الأمواج غضبت أيضًا‬
– Wha...? – Does he wanna fight?
‫ما...؟‬ ‫أيريد القتال؟‬
Boy, that scared me.
‫إنه مرعب‬
Fine. I'll take you on!
‫لا بأس، سأواجهك!‬
Hold it, you guys!
‫تمهّلوا جميعًا‬
Miss Kokoro!
‫كوكورو-سان!‬
It's you who's wrong here, Straw Hat.
‫أنت المخطئ هنا يا قبّعة القشّ‬
Paulie is right, you idiot.
‫باولي محقّ أيّها الغبيّ‬
Shut up! It's none of–
‫اخرسي أيّتها الجدة، ليس من شـ...‬
None of my business... huh?
‫ليس من شأني، صحيح؟‬
Unbelievable...
‫اسمع. إن تركناكم وشأنكم،‬ ‫فستلقون حتفكم‬
Look.
‫ولكن إن كان يوجد سفينة تستطيع عبور أكوا لاغونا،‬
it could only be a sea train built by a legendary man.
‫فلن تكون إلا قطارًا بحريًا بناه رجل أسطوري‬
But it's not here right now!
‫ولكن هذا غير موجود الآن، لذا سنسرق سفينة‬
If you're prepared to die...
‫إن كنتم جاهزين للموت...‬
then come with me.
‫فاتبعوني‬
I'll give you a ride...
‫سأقلّكم على قطار بحريّ!‬
Car 7 (Last Car)
‫المقطورة السابعة‬ ‫(الأخيرة)‬
Car 6 (Freight Car)
‫المقطورة السادسة‬ ‫(مقطورة الشحن)‬
Idiots! What are you doing?!
‫أغبياء! ما الّذي تفعلونه؟!‬
Everyone not in a uniform must be a criminal!
‫إنّ الجميع هنا يرتدون بدل‬ ‫فيما عدى المجرمين!‬
G-Get him!
‫نا-نالوا منه!‬
So it turns out this way anyway, huh?
‫هذا ما آل إليه الأمر في كلّ الأحوال؟‬
I thought I had a good plan...
‫ظننتُ أنّ لديّ خطّة جيّدة...‬
"Operation Play Innocent"...
‫"خطّة التّظاهر بالبراءة"‬
What?! S-Sanji?!
‫ماذا؟ سا-سانجي!‬
– Hold it!
‫مهلًا!‬
– We won't let you pass.
‫لن نسمح لك بالمرور من هنا.‬
Twins, huh?
‫توأم؟‬
Collier...
‫العنق‬ ‫كولير‬
Frite!
‫المقليّ‬ ‫فريت‬
Sanji! Why are you on the sea train?!
‫سانجي! ماذا تفعل على متن القطار البحري؟!‬
I could ask you the same question.
‫أود طرح السؤال نفسه عليك...‬
So what's the story, uh...
‫يا هذا... الّذي لا أعرف ما اسمه...‬
Oh, cut the crap, jerk!
‫لا تتظاهر بأنك لا تعرفني يا وغد‬
There we go! Transponder snails!
‫ها هي، ها هي حلازين الاتّصال!‬
Alright!
‫رائع! ثمة العديد من الأجهزة‬
Probably the communications car...
‫هل هذه غرفة الاتصالات؟‬
Those officials from the car earlier only had junk like masks and costumes!
‫كان لموظّفي الحكومة في المقطورة السابقة‬ ‫أشياء سخيفة كالأقنعة وأزياء تنكرية‬
Now I can finally contact Nami.
‫أستطيع أخيرًا الاتّصال بنامي-سان‬
So you two are pirate crewmates, huh?
‫إذًا فأنتما صديقان في الطاقم نفسه؟‬
– Former crewmates.
‫سابقًا‬
Who the hell are you?
‫من تكون أنت؟‬
I'm Franky the dismantler, boss of the Water Seven underworld.
‫أنا الوجه المُظلم للوتر سيفن... المٌفكك فرانكي!‬
So you're Franky?! You damn bastard!
‫إذًا فأنت هو فرانكي؟ وغد لعين!‬
Who the hell are you to put our Long Nose through hell?!
‫كيف تجرأت على أذيّة زميلنا طويل الأنف؟!‬
How many pieces should I chop you into, asshole?!
‫إلى كم قطعة تريدني‬ ‫أن أقطّعك أيّها الوغد؟!‬
Ah, no, no, no, no, no...
‫مهلًا، مهلًا، مهلًا...‬
S-Sanji, hold on a sec. All sorts of things happened after that.
‫تمهل يا سانجي! حدث الكثير بعد ذلك!‬
You bastard! Just you wait until I'm free!
‫أيّها الوغد! انتظر فحسب حتّى يُفكَّ وثاقي!‬
You've got to stop mouthing off like that!
‫توقّف عن قول أشياء كهذه!‬
Well, he saved the Merry once.
‫حسنًا، لقد أنقذ ميري مرّة‬
Oh, that's right...
‫هذا صحيح... ميري قد...‬
Hey, hey, hold on! This is no time to start moping!
‫مهلًا، تمهل لحظة... هذا ليس وقتًا مناسبًا للحسرة‬
I'm begging you, bro! Please untie me!
‫المهمّ، رجاءً فك وثاقي أيّها الشاب‬
Who'd untie you?! A thug like you should stay like that forever!
‫من قد يفكّ وثاقك؟!‬ ‫يجب أن تظلّ أسيرًا لبقيّة حياتك!‬
You asshole! I asked nicely, and this is how you respond?!
‫أيّها الوغد! كيف تجرؤ على الرفض‬ ‫مع أنّني طلبت بلطف؟!‬
Stop it! You guys!
‫توقّفا كلاكما!‬
If we don't hurry up, they'll find us, right?!
‫إن لم نسرع... فسيكتشفون أمرنا!‬
You're pissing me off!
‫كف عن الثرثرة أيّها الأحمق!‬
What'd you say?!
‫ماذا قلت؟!‬
Shut up, both of you!
‫اخرسا كلاكما‬
Just untie me already!
‫فكّ وثاقي فحسب‬
Captain T-Bone...
‫العقيد تي بون...‬
This warehouse has been abandoned for more than eight years.
‫هذا المستودع مهجور منذ ثمان سنوات‬
Red Brick Warehouse Behind the Waste Facility
‫مستودع الطوب الأحمر‬ ‫خلف منشأة معالجة النفايات‬
And the sea train itself has been untouched for more than twelve.
‫والقطار البحري لم يلمسه أحدٌ منذ أكثر من اثنتي عشر عام‬
Let's go, Chopper!
‫هيّا بنا يا تشوبر‬
Yeah!
‫هيّا‬
Actually, it might not even work anymore!
‫لذا ربما يكون معطلًا أصلًا‬
Hey! That would be a problem!
‫مهلًا! سنكون قد أهدرنا وقتنا!‬
Hey, hey, wait for me.
‫مهلًا، مهلًا، انتظراني‬
Even if you rush ahead, you'll need the keys to get in.
‫حتّى إن كنتم على عجلة من أمركما،‬ ‫لا يمكنكما الدّخول دون مفاتيح‬
Huh? It's already open?
‫ماذا؟ إنّه مفتوح؟‬
There it is!
‫ها هو ذا‬
It looks awesome!
‫يبدو رائعًا!‬
Amazing!
‫مذهل!‬
I'm warning you, this is one crazy train.
‫للتذكير والتحذير، إنه قطار خطِر‬
Its name is Rocketman.
‫اسمه روكيت مان.‬
There's no way we could let paying passengers on this one.
‫يُمنع نقل المسافرين على متنه‬
Rocketman!
‫روكيت مان!‬
It sounds fast!
‫يبدو سريعًا!‬
Cool!
‫مذهل!‬
What's with the face?
‫ما قصّة ذلك الوجه؟‬
The shark head is attached as a joke.
‫أُضيف رأس القرش ذاك كمزحة‬
Iceboss!
‫العمّ أيس!‬
Straw Hat...
‫يسعدني أنك بخير يا قبعة القش‬
Just like that pirate girl said...
‫كانت القرصانة على حقّ‬
Miss Kokoro, you brought them?
‫هل أنتِ من أحضرهم إلى هنا يا كوكورو-سان؟‬
I guess you survived, then, Iceburg?
‫يبدو أنّك نجوت يا أيسبرغ‬
What are you doing here?
‫ماذا تفعل هنا؟‬
If we're both here, it must be for the same reason.
‫إنّ حقيقة تواجدنا هنا معًا‬ ‫تعني أنّه قد راودتنا نفس الفكرة‬
We can't resist helping fools, huh?
‫ألا وهي مساعدة هؤلاء الحمقى‬
Use it.
‫استعملوه‬
I've finished servicing it.
‫فقد انتهيت من إصلاحه‬
I loaded water and coal, and it's building steam now.
‫ملأت مخزن الماء وكذلك الفحم‬ ‫وهو يخزّن البخار في الوقت الحاليّ‬
So you were getting it ready for us, boss?!
‫أكنت تجهّزه لنا أيّها العم؟‬
Save the celebration for after you survive.
‫وفر هذا الابتهاج حتى تعود سالمًا‬
No matter how much maintenance it gets, the steam engine can't limit its speed.
‫يصعب التحكم بسرعة محركه مهما حاولنا إجراء تعديلات...‬
It was a failure from before we finished Puffing Tom.
‫لأنّ روكيت مان يُعد نموذجًا فاشلًا صٌنع قبل إتمام بافينغ توم‬
I can't guarantee your lives.
‫لذا لا أضمن سلامتكم‬
No sweat! Thanks, Iceboss!
‫لا بأس! شكرًا لك أيها العم أيس!‬
Alright! Let's go!
‫إذًا هيّا بنا‬
Guys! Get on board!
‫اصعدوا جميعًا!‬
Lady! We're leaving as soon as Nami comes!
‫أيّتها الجدة، سننطلق حالما تصل نامي‬
Luffy! Are you okay?
‫لوفي! هل أنت بخير؟‬
You've been shaky on your feet for a while.
‫لاحظت أنك تترنّح منذ مدة‬
He probably lost too much blood.
‫أظن لأنّه نزف كثيرًا‬
Yeah, I'm kinda out of energy. If only we had some meat...
‫نعم، أشعر أن طاقتي خارت... ليت لدينا بعض اللحم‬
Hurry! This way!
‫أسرعوا!‬
Wait!
‫مهلًا‬
Why do you need to go to a place like that? Can't you just eat here?
‫ما حاجتُك للذهابِ إلى مكانٍ كهذا؟‬ ‫لماذا لا تأكلين هنا؟‬
That's right! Aren't you starving?!
‫هذا صحيح! ألا تتضوّرين جوعًا؟!‬
As if I could eat all that!
‫أتظن أنني سأتناول كل هذا وحدي؟!‬
– What?!
‫ماذا؟!‬
Sorry for the wait!
‫آسفة لتأخري‬
Nami?
‫نامي؟‬
Hey! What're you doing?!
‫ما الذي كنتِ تفعلينه يا نامي؟‬
Hurry up and get on board, you idiot!
‫اصعدي بسرعة أيّتها الغبية‬
Wow, amazing!
‫هذا مذهل!‬
So this is a sea train, too?
‫أهذا قطارٌ بحريّ أيضًا؟!‬
Whoa... I had no idea there was one in a place like this.
‫لم أكن أعرف بوجود قطار آخر في مكانٍ كهذا‬
What a surprise!
‫يا للمفاجأة‬
Where've you been, Nami?!
‫أين كنتِ يا نامي؟!‬
Wasn't it you who said to hurry up?!
‫ألستِ من قال أنّ الوقت يداهمنا؟!‬
And what's all that stuff?!
‫وما كلّ هذه الأشياء؟!‬
Meat and drinks.
‫لحم ومشروبات‬
I'm sorry that I complained.
‫آسف لأنّني كنت أشتكي‬
Here we go.
‫نحن جاهزون‬
If you can make it onto the railway after getting out to sea via the canal, that'll be a start.
‫إن استطعتِ وضعه على السكة الحديدية بعد خروجكم‬ ‫فسيكون نجاحًا بحد ذاته كبداية‬
Don't worry.
‫لا تقلق، فخبرتي في تشغيله تفوق خبرتك‬
You take it easy and rest here.
‫استرخِ وارتح قليلًا‬
Sorry.
‫أنا آسف‬
Chimney and Gonbe should be playing over there somewhere.
‫تشيمني وغونبي يلعبان في الجوار،‬ ‫اعتنِ بهما رجاءً‬
Straw Hat!
‫يا قبّعة القشّ!‬
They're...
‫إنّهم...‬
...the Franky Family!
‫عائلة فرانكي!‬
At a busy time like this...!
‫لا وقت لدينا للتعامل معهم الآن‬
Please...
‫رجاءً...‬
take us with you!
‫خذونا معكم!‬
I heard from the Galley-La people that you're going to Enies Lobby!
‫سمعتُ من عمّال غاليلا‬ ‫أنّكم ذاهبون لإنيس لوبي!‬
Our Bro, Franky, was taken by the government!
‫اختفطت الحكومة أخانا فرانكي‬
We want to go after them...
‫نريد اللحاق بهم...‬
but we can't get through Aqua Laguna by ourselves!
‫ولكننا لا نستطيع تجاوز أكوا لاغونا وحدنا!‬
It's the World Government you're up against.
‫أتدرون أنكم بصدد تحدّي حكومة العالم؟‬
It doesn't matter who it is!
‫لا يهمنا من سنتحدى!‬
We're gonna get Bro back!
‫سنستعيد أخانا‬
We'd give up our lives for him!
‫إننا مستعدون للتضحية بأرواحنا في سبيل استعادته‬
Please!
‫أرجوكم!‬
Help us out!
‫ساعدنا يا قبّعة القشّ!‬
Please! Bro is in danger!
‫أرجوك، فأخونا في خطر‬
Give me a break!
‫أتمازحوننا؟‬
Do you realize what you've put us through?!
‫ألا تدركون حجم المتاعب التي سببتموها لنا؟!‬
We do!
‫بلى‬
We're swallowing our pride and begging you!
‫لكننا تخلينا عن كبريائنا ولجأنا إليكم‬
We want to save Bro!
‫نريد إنقاذ أخانا‬
Get on.
‫اركبوا‬
Hurry!
‫بسرعة!‬
Straw Hat...
‫قبعة القش‬
Hey, Luffy!
‫مهلًا يا لوفي‬
Oh, it'll be fine.
‫لا تقلقي‬
Thank you!
‫شكرًا جزيلًا‬
We're deeply indebted to you!
‫إنّنا مدينون لك‬
Hurry up!
‫أسرعوا!‬
But we don't have to get on the train!
‫ولكن لا داعي لركوب القطار معكم‬
We'll jump out to sea on our king bulls when you do!
‫سنمطتي الثيران الملكية ثم نقفز إلى البحر‬
Just let us hitch a ride on the back of your train.
‫لذا كل ما نحتاجه منكم هو السماح لنا بالتشبث بنهاية القطار‬
King bulls?
‫الثيران الملكية؟‬
Thanks for letting us come!
‫شكرًا على الموافقة!‬
Well then, see you later!
‫نراكم بعد قليل‬
Let's go!
‫لنذهب!‬
– Yeah!
‫أجل‬
Alright! We can go rescue Bro!
‫أجل! بإمكاننا إنقاذ أخينا!‬
Hurry up!
‫أسرعوا!‬
How's this?
‫كيف هي الآن؟‬
Okay!
‫حسنًا، هيّا بنا ننطلق!‬
Now, pirates!
‫والآن أيّها القراصنة! إيّاكم أن تُرموا‬ ‫من القطار، مفهوم؟!‬
Now departing Water Seven for Enies Lobby...
‫ها نحن نغادر ووتر سيفن متجهين إلى إنيس لوبي‬
Here comes the sea train Rocketman!
‫ها هو قطار روكيت مان منطلق!‬
Alright! We're off!
‫حسنًا! لننطلق!‬
Let's go...
‫ها نحن قادمون...‬
and take everything back!
‫لاستعادة كل شيء!‬